The crash ice game was a lot of fun and I would like to start the second round.
As a point of reflection, too much ice was accumulating at the bottom, so once you drop it, let's take it out already.
I would like to continue with the style of pulling out the ice.
I would like to continue in that style.
I will continue to do so, because I don't want to take out only the part supported by the ice below.
I would like to do that.
Next, Yuzuki.
First, Yuzuki.
And then... oh...
Oh, it's out.
Thank you very much.
I'll start from the end.
I'll go first.
Oh, my God.
It's already starting to move.
It's a little dangerous.
It's dangerous.
Ah.
Okay, then.
Here we go.
Eh...
Oh.
Eh.
Huh.
That's...
OK.
Okay, then.
You're getting a little bold, aren't you?
Ah! Smile!
Oh, my God, it's going, it's going, it's going, it's going.
Isn't that it?
The ice is getting bolder, too.
Hey!
It's already open, you know.
It's coming.
It's not moving at all, but it's moving!
Isn't it too special? The way you hit it.
It's like this...it goes sideways.
Oh, it's just one. That's good.
It just hit me.
Two.... Now I'll drop two more.
Oh, they didn't fall. They didn't fall. They didn't fall.
OK. Okay, where should we go?
Let's go around here.
It's still pretty safe around here, isn't it?
Yes, it's fine. It's still pretty safe.
There's a lot of density.
Oh, wow!
I got it in three beats.
It's about to get bad, isn't it?
Good, good, good, good.
It's good.
I'm going to go for it.
Oh, wow!
But no thanks.
Momentum is important.
Momentum is good.
Yes, it's good.
That's good.
Oh! I thought I might fall. Surprisingly.
Three down. The ice is getting a little aggressive.
Oh, no! All of them!
Dare, dare.
That's smart. Dare.
Here.
Ah!
I lost my arrowhead again.
Maybe I'm weak.
There's a lot of ice left.
I thought momentum was important, but it wasn't that important.
Height was important.
Art won again.
It was me.
It's fun, isn't it?
I hope you all play the game again, taking pictures of this and that.
Bye bye.